Priyanka Raj Front Office Operations

rajpriyanka117@gmail.com

+91-9997607689

DEHRADUN, INDIA 🔾

linkedin.com/in/rajpriyanka117@gmail.com in

instagram.com/dangwal.priyanka 🧿

Adaptable Front Desk Receptionist with experience Hotel industry and a history of success in providing exceptional customer service. Experience in managing all facts of front office administration, including handling multi-line phone systems, managing schedules, and maintaining reception and waiting areas. Hands-on skills in using applications such as MS Office, Opera and IDS to facilitate daily office operations.

EDUCATION

DIPLOMA IN AVIATION, HOSPITALITY &CUSTOMER SERVICE

FRANKFINN INSTITUTE OF AIR HOSTESS TRAINING

NEW DELHI

INTERMEDIATE

JAWAHAR NAVODAYA VIDHYALAYA 2015.

HIGH SCHOOL

JAWAHAR NAVODAYA VIDHYALAYA 2013.

WORK EXPERIENCE

PRASAD HERITAGE GROUP

SENIOR SUPERVISOR

Aloha On The Ganges, Rishikesh (U.K.)

11/2019 - 09/2020

FRONT OFFICE EXECUTIVE

The Naini Retreat, Nainital (U.K.)

09/2020 till date

GUEST RELATION EXECUTIVE

ITC WELCOMHOTEL THE SAVOY, Mussoorie

09/2017 - 06/2019,

FRONT OFFICE ASSOCIATE

RADISSON BLU HOTEL, Haridwar

12/2016 - 09/2017,

STRENGTH

- Good guest interaction skills.
- Leadership/People management.
- Good interpersonal and communication skills.
- Tenacious, Independent and willing to take initiative.
- A team player, continuous learner and proactive.

SKILLS

HOSPITALITY TEAM LEADERSHIP

MICROSOFT OFFICE INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

ABILITY TO MULTITASK CUSTOMER RELATION

MANAGEMENT SKILLS

CERTIFICATES

*Awarded as "Bravo" in Radisson Blu Hotel.

*Awarded as "Best Groomed Employee" in RadissonBlu Hotel.

*Awarded as "Best Guest Experienced Award" in WelcomHotel The Savoy.

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH
HINDI
LOCAL

INTERESTS

VOLLEY BALL SINGING DANCING

READING EXPLORING OUTDOOR GAMES